<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>superoo7</title>
    <link>http://www.superoo7.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on superoo7</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:21:52 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.superoo7.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chasm Network Scout Hosting Tutorial</title>
      <link>http://www.superoo7.com/posts/chasm-network-scout-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:21:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.superoo7.com/posts/chasm-network-scout-hosting/</guid>
      <description>In this guide, I will walk you through the process of running Chasm Scout in Season 0 using Digital Ocean. Please note that you should always refer to the Official Guide for the most up-to-date information.&#xA;This guide aims to provide a simple, step-by-step approach for those unfamiliar with Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs).&#xA;Step 1: Mint NFT to Get Scout ID and API Key Link to heading Visit https://scout.chasm.net&#xA;Step 2: Get Groq API Key Link to heading Visit https://console.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.superoo7.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:20:18 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://www.superoo7.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Johnson Lai Self-taught engineer and UWA alum, currently Cofounder/CTO at Chasm Network (decentralized AI). Former COO/CTO at Hooga Gaming and R&amp;amp;D &amp;amp; mobile engineer at CoinGecko. Passionate about blockchain, AI, and building product.&#xA;Previous experience Link to heading [11/2023 - Now] Chasm Network Cofounder &amp;amp; CTO [06/2021 - 11/2023] Hooga Gaming COO CTO [2022] Pacer Head Of Product Product Advisor [2020] ETHKL Co-Organizer [12/2018 - 02/2022] CoinGecko Software Engineer Product Engineer Senior Mobile Engineer Senior R&amp;amp;D Engineer [06/2017 - 01/2018] PhytoMark Fullstack Software Engineer My work Link to heading Publication Link to heading Chasm Protocol: Pioneering the evolution of AI with Decentralized Panel of Experts and Blockchain Integration (2024) State Transfer on Polygon for moving assets from L2 to L1 trustlessly (Feb 10, 2023) Understanding Risk of Rebase Tokens Through Smart Contract Analysis (August 16, 2020) Behind The scene of CoinGecko DeFi Page (August 1, 2020) RxJS for building UI (August 12, 2018) Talks Link to heading Breaking Down the Current State of Decentralized AI (Jun 5, 2024) The Synergy of AI and Web 3 (Jun 17, 2023) Dead Man Switch&amp;rsquo;s Smart Contract (Feb 6, 2020) How NFT works?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
